<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
	<item>
		<content><![CDATA[

<span class="title">Neobux - #1 PTC</span>
				
<p align="justify">Neobux is without a doubt one of the most profitable PTC Programs on the web. They have been established since 2008, and they have not stopped changing and evolving since then. Most PTC users have either heard of Neobux or are already members.
As of this year, they have over 20 Million members and they're still growing their network. They have paid over <span class="highlight">$80 Million</span> in cashouts, and this proves without a doubt that they are a legit, paying company.

<a href="http://www.neobux.com/?r=yakinus" target="_blank">Join Neobux Now</a>

They have various new features, such as <span class="highlight">getting paid to do tasks and offers</span>, as well as the ability to make <span class="highlight">commissions</span> when one of your downline completes an offer. </p>	

<span class="title">Clixsense</span>

<p align="justify">This site has been established and paying since 2007. Some consider it the best PTC in the industry. With Clixsense you can earn from 8 levels of referrals. Each time someone in your downline upgrades, you can make $1 to $2.

<span class="note">Note: Under the first level you can only make money from member's upgrades.</span>

<a href="http://www.clixsense.com/?2300171" target="_blank">Join Clixsense Now</a>

Clixsense pays you 0.01 to 0.02 per click, which is a pretty good rate compared to most other sites. You can also get paid to do tasks and surveys. The pay depends on the survey and task performed.</p> 

<span class="title">Wordlinx</span>

<p align="justify">Wordlinx is a pay to click site that has been paying for many years. That's a great accomplishment for any PTC site. Make up to 0.01 per click and earn from 10 levels of referrals.</span>

<a href="http://wordlinx.net/?r=495774" target="_blank">Join Wordlinx Now</a>

There are also some great advertising options in Wordlinx, so check it out today

<span class="title">DownlineRefs.com</span> 
	
<p align="justify">DownlineRefs is a downline builder designed to get you referrals for your favorite PTC websites. It's completely free to sign up and you can earn credits right away.
By joining other sites you can earn lots of credits, which can be used to build your own downline.
<a href="http://www.downlinerefs.com/?ref=yakinus" target="_blank">Join DownlineRefs Now</a> 
You can also upgrade to get special features not accessible to standard members.
</p>

<span class="title">ProfitClicking</span>

<p align="justify">ProfitClicking is a traffic exchange site that delivers traffic to your websites. For $10 you can get 1,000 hits to your website. You can refer other members and make 2% commissions for 81 days.
There's also a chance to earn 10% commissions from your first level referrals and 5% commissions from your 2nd level referrals from their purchased ad traffic packages.</span>
<a href="http://www.profitclicking.com/?r=zZBxX5jbpm" target="_blank">Join ProfitClicking Now</a>
This site has been established since 2004, and since its inception, they have delivered billions of clicks to their members.
</p> 

<span class="title">TrafficAdBar</span>

<p align="justify">Get 1,022 visits to your website every 3 days for FREE at TrafficAdBar 
<a href="http://trafficadbar.com/yakinus">Join TrafficAdBar</a></p>


<span class="title">Neobux Ultimate Strategy</span>


<p align="justify">Learn how to make $20 to $30 a day from PTC Websites by getting unlimited direct referrals
<a href="http://neobuxultimatestrategy.com/?r=yakinus">Get the NUS Now</a>
</p> 

]]></content>
	</item>
</items>